我们可以去车上待着...
We could jump in the car if...
在这儿等着
We'll wait.
-你给议员买生日礼物了吗  -没有
- Did you get the congressman anything for his birthday? - No.
我买了袖口  银质的  有他的...
I got him cufflinks. Silver, with his --
我们不谈论生日  不送礼物
We don't talk about birthdays. We don't do gifts.
为什么
Why not?
去把袖口退了吧
You should return the cufflinks.
道格
Doug?
我一直在给你打电话
Tried calling you.
-我把手机留在...  -我们得谈谈
- I left my phone in the... - We need to talk.
怎么了
What's going on?
克里斯蒂娜  我刚刚跟她谈过
Christina. I just spoke to her.
佐伊...
Did Zoe...?
是的  但还不止
Yeah. But that's not all.
他们还找到了瑞秋
They tracked down Rachel, too.
弗兰西斯
Francis?
跟我说说瑞秋  她在哪
Tell me about Rachel. Where is she?
我控制住她了
I have her under control.
答非所问
That's not what I asked.
我送她回家了  不用担心她
I drove her home. We don't have to worry about her.
你当初也这么说斯克斯基
You said the same about Ms. Skorsky.
还牵扯到别人了吗
Anyone else involved?
只有简宁和佐伊
Just Janine and Zoe.
他们在查罗素被捕的事
They asked about Russo's arrest
而且知道他去找过科佩尼科
and they know he went to see Kapeniak.
我想他们应该就知道这些了
I assume that's as far as they've gotten.
不要想当然
Assume nothing.
我去告诉巴尼·豪尔
I'll alert Barney Hull.
拿佐伊怎么办
What do you want me to do about Zoe?
我对付佐伊
I'll handle Zoe.
你去办事吧
Get to work.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
我拿走了
I emptied it.
你周二就又老一岁了
You're another year older on Tuesday.
副总统可不能抽烟
And we can't have a vice president who smokes.
你能结束吗
Can you finish?
什么
What?
我完事了
I'm good.
你怎么了
What's wrong?
没什么  就是完事了
Nothing. I just said finish.
我不想...如果你不想...
Well, I don't want just -- if you're not...
好吧  随便了
Okay, fine. Whatever.
佐伊  是我做错了什么吗
Zoe, did I do something that made you...?
没有
No.
佐伊  你不能说一句完事了  然后就停下啊
Zoe, you can't say something like "just finish" and then shut down.
这里很安全  佐伊  我不是他
This is safe, Zoe. I'm not him.
早上好  杰姬
Good morning, Jackie.
早上好
Good morning.
理查德·拉塞尔
Richard Russell.
长期反对民权运动
1963年  《民权法案》
Civil Rights Act. 1963.
不是所有人都能青史留名
Not everyone can be on the right side of history.
连林登也曾站错队
No, not even Lyndon for a time,
但没有拉塞尔  林登也当不上多数党领袖
but he would have never become majority leader without him.
但是没有约翰逊参议院大楼
Well, there's no Johnson Senate building.
有拉塞尔参议院大楼
是啊  只能委屈他拿一栋总统图书馆凑合了
No. He had to settle for a presidential library.
我们都好久没聊聊了
So it's been some time since you and I have had a chance to catch up.
你的工作做得很出色  杰姬
You've been an outstanding deputy, Jackie.
比你那些老练的同事还高效
Far more effective than your more seasoned colleagues.
你能推动合作  必要时候还有股狠劲
You're a coalition builder, a fighter when you have to be.
告诉我  你怎么看自己的前途
Tell me, where do you see yourself headed?
我想做众议院军事委员会主席
I'd like to aim for the chair of Armed Services.
或者众议院国土安全委员会主席
Or Homeland Security.
你考虑过进入领导层吗
Have you ever considered serving in the leadership?
我想那至少也得等八...十年了
I figure that might be possible eight, ten years from now.
如果我说你这一届就能进入领导层呢
Well, what if I suggested that you could serve in leadership this term.
接替我  做党鞭
To replace me. As whip.
你要接任副总统了
You're being tapped for VP.
就算是这样吧
Let's assume that's true.
-这也说得通  但我做党鞭  -是的
- Well, that makes sense. But me as whip? - Yes.
我只是个第三任女议员
A third-term congresswoman?
你的能力有目共睹  而且还参过战
A universally admired incumbent who also happens to be a war veteran.
按顺序也该是韦伯  或巴克沃特
Webb is next in line. Or Buchwalter.
所以  你考虑一下吧
So just consider that for a moment.
他们会牵制彼此的选票
They'll draw votes from one another.
我可没说你会赢得很轻松
Oh, I'm not saying you wouldn't have to fight for it,
但我愿意帮你
but I'd be willing to give you the ammunition.
过来
Come over here.
这是什么
What is this?
我关于韦伯和巴克沃特的文件
My files on Webb and Buchwalter.
你自己看看吧
Why don't you take a look?
我们过几天再谈
We'll speak in a few days.
还有一个关于你的文件夹
Oh, and, uh, there's one on you.
或许你会想先读那个
You might want to begin by reading that one first.
简宁怎么说
What'd Janine say?
脱衣舞俱乐部还没开
Strip club's not open yet.
你去查科佩尼科的事吗
You'll look into Kapeniak?
如果他出现  我就能找到他
If he's on the grid, I'll find him.
-送我去地铁中心站  -不去办公室吗
- Drop me at metro center. - Not the office?
我要去找瑞秋
I'm gonna talk to Rachel.
她会像昨晚那样否认一切的
She'll deny everything, like she did last night.
她不能否认上了斯坦普的车  你看到她了
She can't deny getting into Stamper's car. You saw her.
或许你可以写一篇关于她爸爸的事的报道
Maybe you send a version of the story, about her dad?
没人会发表的
No one would print it.
可瑞秋不知道啊
Rachel doesn't know that.
她说"随你便  贱人"
She said, "Go to town, bitch."
不会管用的  我得当面跟她谈
It won't work. I have to get in her face.
恭喜
Congratulations.
-我们都替你高兴  -谢谢
- We're thrilled for you. - Thank you.
我想亲自跟鲍勃和泰瑞说
I wanted to fill in Bob and Terry personally.
我们快开始吧  我什么时候出发去匹兹堡
Now let's get to it. I have to leave for Pittsburgh in what?
20分钟后
20 minutes.
帮吉姆冲刺  就要到终点了
Home stretch with Jim. Whistle-stop tour.
现在形势很好
Looking good out there.
的确  但我们还是不想冒险
Very good. But we don't want to take any chances.
接替你的党鞭人选  弗兰克
Now, your replacement as whip, Frank.
鲍勃已经提出了一些想法
Bob has already shared some thoughts.
我喜欢霍华德·韦伯
I like Howard Webb.
韦伯不错  你考虑过韦斯·巴克沃特吗
Webb is a solid choice. Have you thought about Wes Buchwalter?
巴克沃特太冲动
Buchwalter's a hot-head.
那么韦伯你觉得可以吗  弗兰克
Well, could you live with Webb, Frank?
韦伯懂战术  但做事虎头蛇尾
Webb is a good tactician, but he lacks follow-through.
巴克沃特是个粗人
The problem with Buchwalter is he's too abrasive.
毫无魅力  树敌太多
No charm. Lots of enemies.
还有别的选择吗
Is there a third option?
他们是党团资历最深的两位  轮到他们了
They're the two most senior members in the caucus. It's their turn.
总统先生  可不可以让党内成员一起挑选
Mr. President, what if we let the caucus pick?
大家公平竞争  他们两人都很有资质
Let it be a wide-open race. Both men are qualified.
领导层在这事上要意见一致
The leadership should be united in this.
我们不能各自支持不同的候选人  弗兰克
We don't want to be backing different candidates, Frank.
那我们就干脆别插手  谁都不支持
So we stay out of it and neither of us backs anyone.
这挺好
I like it.
党团会尊重凭实力竞争上来的人
Caucus will respect someone who did it the old-fashioned way.
几位  这事你们做主
Well, gentlemen, it's your call to make.
你们自己讨论决定  然后告诉我
Figure it out amongst yourselves. Let me know what you decide.
谢谢  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
帮我接刘易斯部长
Put me through to Secretary Lewis.
弗兰克  我不想为这事跟你争
Frank, I don't want to go to battle with you on this.
我们犯过这种错
We've been down that road.
说得是啊
I couldn't agree more.
公平竞争让我紧张
An open race makes me nervous.
我只是提议一下
Well, look, it was just a suggestion.
-我再想想吧  -谢谢
- I'll put some thought into it. - Thank you.
我去做做他的工作吧
You know, let me -- let me go work on him.
祝你好运了
Good luck.
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
问我要点什么
Ask me what I want to order.
想好点什么了吗  先生
Have you decided, sir?
你马上辞职  告诉里昂你不干了
I need you to quit your job. Tell Leon it's your last day.
为什么
Why?
表现自然点
Act normal.
要什么配菜
Did you want a side with that?
他们能找到你一次
They found you once.
不能冒险让你再被找到
We can't take the chance they'll find you again.
那钱的事怎么办
What am I supposed to do about money?
照我说的做  回家  收拾东西
Do as I say. Go home and pack your things.
我十点过来
I'll come by around ten.
-那我就无权决定...  -够了
- Well -- but I don't get a say in any... - Stop it.
只收拾一个箱子
One suitcase. That's it.
-你至少也告诉我...  -我要肉馅土豆馅饼
- Can you at least tell me... - I'll take the shepherd's pie
配菜要球芽甘蓝
with a side of Brussels sprouts.
带走
To go.
我们不想上法庭  她的律师不想上法庭
We don't want a trial. Her lawyers don't want a trial.
但科尔女士就是不听劝
But Ms. Cole won't listen to reason.
即便如此  如果你再给我点时间
That said, if you give me a little more time, I think that --
如果她想上法庭  那就随她
If she wants to go to court, then let's give her that.
虽然她现在不肯讲理  不代表将来...
Just because she's being unreasonable now doesn't mean she --
我受够了
I'm done.
这就是膝跳反应
That's a knee-jerk reaction.
我知道你不是个不理智不耐心的人
I've never known you to be a person who was irrational or impatient.
我再去找找她的律师  或许我们...
Let me check back with her lawyers, and maybe we can --
最早什么时候能知道开庭日期
What's the soonest we can get a trial date?
克莱尔
Claire...
给我个大致时间
Give me a timeframe.
最早也六个月后吧
Six months, at the earliest.
转告她那边  然后就中止沟通
Inform her people, then no more communication.
作为你的律师  我有责任强烈建议你不要这么做
As your counsel, it is my duty to strongly advise you against this.
我明白  谢谢你  奥利弗
I understand and I thank you, Oliver.
谢谢
Thank you.
-怎么样  -他们不肯透露私人联络方式
- So? - They wouldn't give me individual contact info,
但这里是过去三年在东非工作过的
but here's every doctor who served in east Africa
所有医生的名单
during the last three years.
健康维护组织呢
And what about the HMO?
收取固定预付费用后  为特定地区主动参保人群提供全面医疗服务的体系
需要同意书  也在袋子里了
You need a consent form. And it's in the packet.
私人医师  东非
大卫·阿普博姆医生
有事吗
Can I help you?
我找瑞秋·波斯纳
Yeah. I'm looking for Rachel Posner.
她不在
She's not here.
她晚些时候会来吗
Uh, is she coming in later?
干什么
Why?
我认识她
I know her.
你朋友可把我害惨了
Well, your friend really screwed me over.
怎么回事
What happened?
她上班上到一半就跑了
She took off, middle of her shift.
我不得不去找我的房东来帮忙
I had to put my hostess on wait staff duty.
我有点担心  瑞秋有麻烦
Look, I'm concerned. Rachel's in real trouble.
我才不管她的私人问题呢
I don't care what her personal issues are.
我只想知道她住哪
I just need to know where she lives.
你们不是认识吗
I thought you knew her.
我们认识  但有日子没见了
I do. It's just been a while.
她给我发短信说她想自残
And she sent me a text message saying she wants to hurt herself.
现在又不接电话
And now she won't answer her phone.
她有精神病史
She has a history of mental illness.
你得帮帮我啊
You've gotta help me out.
我帮不了
Look, I can't.
她的工资和税务报表  上面的地址是个邮箱
Her W-2, the address is a P.O. Box.
有什么都行
I'll take whatever I can get.
-我去办公室帮你看看  -谢谢
- Let me see what I got in the office. - Thank you.
如果你找的她  叫她别回来了
If you find her, you tell her not to come back.
我才不需要疯子来我这儿捣乱
I don't need some nutcase creating chaos in here.
-南茜  -是  先生
- Nancy? - Yes, sir?
道格回来了吗
Is Doug back yet?
在办公室  还有
In his office. And, sir?
我们开始收到生日贺卡了  还有几件礼物
Birthday cards have started to arrive. A few presents.
写感谢信  记录礼物  贵重的...
Thank you notes. Inventory the presents. Anything valuable...
摆进会议室
Goes in the conference room?
便宜的...
Anything cheap...
给实习生
Goes to the interns.
你知道怎么处理贺卡
And you know what to do with the cards.
当然
Yes, sir.
我今晚去接她
I'm picking her up tonight.
我在乔帕都安排好了
I got everything set up for her in Joppa.
那是哪里
Where's that?
马里兰  巴尔的摩北30分钟路程
Maryland. About 30 minutes north of Baltimore.
太近了
That's close to home.
我们想让她消失  但我们得能找到她
We want her to disappear, but not on us.
-好吧  一次性电话买好了吗  -嗯
- Fine. Do you have the burner? - Yeah.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
预付款的  你只要开机拨号就行
It's prepaid. All you need to do is turn it on and dial.
电话记录还得处理掉
We still have the phone history.
所以日后更要小心了
All the more reason to be safe going forward.
克里斯蒂娜怎么样了
Where are we with Christina?
我在办
I'm on it.
安排她去琳达手下  我今早打过电话了
Linda's office. I called her this morning.
你是吉莉安·科尔吗
Are you Gillian Cole?
是的  我们认识吗
Yeah. Uh, have we met?
没有  但你认识我丈夫
No, we haven't met. You know my husband.
你丈夫
Your husband?
大卫·阿普博姆
David Applebaum.
看来是真的喽
So it's true.
那只是个错误
It was a mistake.
你想看看我们的孩子吗  我可以给你看看照片
You want to see our kids? I can show you pictures.
阿普博姆太太  我...
Mrs. Applebaum, I -- I'm...
你以为你是谁啊
Who the fuck do you think you are?
我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
你抱歉  我觉得你并不抱歉
You're sorry? I don't think you're sorry.
而且你也休想
And don't think for a second
凭这个孩子来向我们要钱
you're gonna use that baby to get money out of us.
他根本不知道我怀孕了
He doesn't even know I'm pregnant.
但你知道他是有妇之夫
But you knew he was married.
你怎么能这样
How could you?
-他说起过我们吗  -没有
- Did he talk about us? - No.
说谎的婊子  我让你难堪了吗
Lying bitch. Am I embarrassing you?
你想过这对我和我孩子的羞辱吗
Did you think about how you would humiliate me and my kids?
再跟别人老公上床记得戴套
Use a condom the next time you fuck somebody's husband.
还不到24个小时
It's been less than 24 hours.
她正在上班就突然辞职了
She quits her job in the middle of a shift?
她害怕了
She's scared.
换了我也会跑
I'd take off, too.
是安德伍德
It's Underwood.
他行动比我们快
He's moving faster than we are.
脱衣舞女呢
What about the stripper?
不肯开口
Refuses to talk.
科佩尼科呢
Kapeniak?
住址不详  没兄弟姐妹  父母双亡
No current address. No siblings. Parents are dead.
瑞秋是唯一的机会
Rachel's the last loose end.
除了酒驾  她肯定还知道点别的
She must know something else. Bigger than the DUI.
知道她去哪了吗
Any idea where she went?
有个杜邦的邮箱地址  但管理员都没见过她
I got a P.O. Box in Dupont, but none of the clerks have seen her.
我可以去那里守株待兔
I could go stake it out, but...
你找过你的人了吗
Have you talked to your guy yet?
明后天吧
In the next day or two.
他会把罗素自杀的警方报告拿给我
He's bringing me the police report on Russo's suicide.
我尽量多套些信息
I'll press him for more.
你下一步怎么办
And what's your next move?
想想怎么回复这个
Trying to figure out how to respond to this.
周一下午三点  地点你定
几个小时前收到的
I got it a couple hours ago.
他是在给你下套
I think he's setting her up.
我知道怎么应付他
I know how to handle him.
他知道的越少越好
The less he learns, the better.
我们也许能打探到消息
We might learn something.
是他说了算  怎么打探
Not with him calling the shots.
地点是我定
I'm choosing the place.
有什么区别
As if that makes a difference.
我又不会跟他上床  就是谈话
I'm not gonna fuck him. Just talk to him.
我去下洗手间
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
-抱歉  我不该  -没关系
- I'm sorry. I shouldn't have -- - That's okay.
有关系
No, it's not.
我不希望你疏忽大意
I just don't want you to be careless.
不会的
I won't be.
你不想有自己的生活
You want no life?
想一个人做三个人的工作吗
You want more work than three people can handle?
你想找个第一个月
You want a decent chance
就可能被炒的工作吗
that you could be fired within the first month?
如果你感兴趣  咱就接着谈
If that tempts you, we can keep talking.
那些都不是问题
None of that intimidates me.
过去九周里我都在管理一个选区
I've been running a congressional district for the past nine weeks
而且没人帮我
with zero assistance.
没人选举我
Nobody elected me.
没人教我怎么做
Nobody taught me.
我那么做是因为总得有人来做
I've done it because somebody had to.
罗素的事是个悲剧
What happened was tragic.
可我不会同情你
But you won't get sympathy from me.
我没有时间
I don't have time for it.
我要是想博取同情  也不会到这儿来
I wouldn't be sitting here if I wanted a shoulder to cry on.
瑞秋
Rachel?
走开
Leave.
我说走开
I said leave.
打包好了吗
Are you packed?
我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
你今天没辞职
So you didn't quit today.
辞了  可我改主意了
I did, but I changed my mind.
这事由不得你
This isn't your decision to make.
我要回去工作  继续住这儿
I'm keeping my job and I'm keeping this apartment.
不行
No, you're not.
你答应过  会让这些都过去
You promised you'd make all of this go away.
所以你得重新开始
And you starting over is the first --
我已经重新开始了  不想再来一次了
No, I already started over. I don't want to start over again.
我也不想你这样
I wish you didn't have to.
滚出去
Get out.
Get out!
小点声
Lower your voice.
我杀了你
I'll fucking kill you.
动手吧
Go ahead.
只有我能保护你  你还不明白吗
I am the only one who can protect you. Don't you see that?
你不知道自己现在多危险
You have no idea how much danger you're in.
收拾东西吧
Start packing.
我每年都得问一句
You know I ask every year.
不过生日  像往年一样
Nothing, as usual.
我们可以吃顿晚餐
I thought we could have dinner.
除非是去个没人会认出我们的地方
Only if it's someplace where nobody will recognize us.
我不想谁走过来...
I don't want anyone walking up --
我是说在家  我可以做点菜
I mean at home. I'll cook something.
不要蛋糕
No cake.
不买蛋糕
不要礼物
No gifts.
不买礼物
那行  诉讼怎么样了
I can do that. How's the lawsuit coming?
我们不会有事的
We'll be fine.
我们打算将您的安保规模
We'd like to increase the size of your detail
增至国家元首级别  从明天开始
to full head of state status, starting tomorrow.
这可不行
Well, that won't be happening.
提前准备总是没错的
It's good to get a head start,
这样等他们宣布...
so that by the time they announce --
在我彻底失去隐私之前就剩这几天了
These are my last few days before I never have privacy again.
我要尽量好好享受这几天
I intend to savor these moments for as long as I can.
但是先生  出于安全考虑  我认为...
But, sir, in terms of safety, I think --
在正式宣布由我接任副总统之前
Until I'm confirmed as the Vice President,
安保问题仍是我来决定  对吗
security is at my discretion. Is that correct?
理论上是的  但是...
Technically, yes. But --
那不就得了
Then that's settled.
那好吧  我们等正式宣布
All right. We'll wait until the announcement.
那么  正式宣布之后
Now, assuming the confirmation goes through,
我们就要解决您搬入
we'll need to work out the logistics
海军天文台的后勤工作
of moving you into the Naval Observatory.
天文台地界内的"天文台一号圈"为美国副总统官邸
这也不行
That won't be happening, either.
议员会继续住在他的别墅里
The congressman will be remaining in his townhouse.
但那里没有必要的安保基建
But it doesn't have the necessary security infrastructure.
那你们就去建啊
Then you'll need to build it.
要建防爆设施
We're talking blast-proofing,
固定线路通信网络  24小时办公室空间
hardwired communications networks, 24-hour office space --
有志者事竟成
Where there's a will, there's a way.
我会直接跟你联络  讨论改建计划
I'll contact you directly about setting a plan in motion.
你走之前  还有件事
And one last thing before you go.
把艾德华·密查姆安排在我的安保队伍里
I'd like to have Edward Meechum serve on my detail.
他是国会警察
He's Capitol Police.
目前是  你要派他去特勤处
For now. You're about to appoint him to the Secret Service.
那得经过加速训练培训
That would require an accelerated training program.
先生  我们有很多合格的特工
Sir, we have plenty of qualified agents.
有男有女  都有丰富经验
Men and women with years of experience.
我很期待与他们合作
And I look forward to working with all of them,
只要艾德华·密查姆也是安保队一员就行
as long as Edward Meechum is on the detail.
多谢你前来
Thank you very much for your time.
谢谢你  先生
Thank you, sir.
佐伊·巴恩斯  石溪公园
我就来
南茜  让密查姆把车开过来
Nancy, have Meechum bring the car around.
上一次就是最后一次
You know, the last time was the last time.
我知道  但这很重要
I know. But this is important.
你总想拉我下水  我不干了
You keep selling me that swampland. I'm done buying.
再也不干了
No more.
掩盖案件的事  你说能牵扯到巴尼·豪尔
Cover-up. You said it went as high as Barney Hull.
我不是那么说的
That's not what I said.
你把瑞秋·波斯纳的拘捕记录给我时...
When you gave me Rachel Posner's arrest file --
我说的是  肯定有大人物干预  记录才会消失
What I said is that arrests don't disappear without a big-ass wand.
那可不能当做证据
That ain't the same as proof.
我们认为这事牵扯到议会领导层
We think the congressional leadership took part.
我才不关心
I don't care.
不  你关心  我知道你关心的
Yes, you do. I know you do.
不  我真的不关心
No, I really don't.
当年你帮我暴露毒品...
When you helped me expose the drug --
他们不过是拿点小恩小惠的街头黑警
They were dirty street cops stuffing a few grams in their pockets.
这事可不一样  都是有权有势的大人物
This is different. Powerful fucking people.
黑警就是黑警  你想保护他们吗
Dirty cops are dirty cops. You want to protect them?
我还有养老保险和家人
I have a pension and a family.
我明白  但是...
I understand. But --
不要再联系我了
Don't contact me again.
死者坐在车子的副驾座上
卢卡斯·古德温至佐伊·巴恩斯  警方报告说罗素是在副驾座上
佐伊·巴恩斯  还有别的吗
卢卡斯·古德温  没了
佐伊·巴恩斯  这证明不了什么
卢卡斯·古德温  他怎么没在正驾座上
佐伊·巴恩斯  不聊了
你的手机在哪
Where's your cell?
这里  我没在录音
Here. It's not recording.
你得删掉我们之间所有的通话记录
I need to ask you to delete all of our phone history.
我为什么要删掉
Why would I do that?
我这是在保护我们两个人
I'm trying to protect both you and I.
要坐牢的又不是我
I'm not facing prison.
他酒驾不是你替他掩盖的吗
You didn't cover up the arrest?
是不是因为你想让他竞选州长
Is it because you wanted him to be governor?
不是  他惹了麻烦  我就伸了援手
No. He was in trouble, so I helped.
之后他表现出参选意愿  我就提供了指导
And later he expressed a desire to run, and I offered guidance.
指导一个酒鬼吗
To an alcoholic?
他当时戒了酒  正在恢复中
To a sober recovering alcoholic.
你是指望他会自毁前程吗
Did you want him to self-sabotage?
当然不是
Absolutely not.
他没戏了  马修斯才来参选
It got Matthews in the race.
我愿意支持有上进心的人
I like to back people who want to succeed.
比如说你自己
Take yourself as an example.
你不过是渔翁得利
You just took advantage of the situation.
得利的是马修斯  我没非要当副总统啊
Matthews took advantage. I didn't seek the nomination.
罗素死的时候坐在副驾座上
Russo was in the passenger seat when he died.
这话不准确
That's not entirely accurate.
我看过警方报告
I saw the police report.
我还直接和警局局长谈过呢
And I spoke to the commissioner directly,
因为我关心彼得  我想了解全部细节
because I cared about Peter and I wanted to know the full story.
那他没坐在副驾座上吗
He wasn't in the passenger seat?
副驾座的车门开着  他半边身子躺在外面
The passenger door was open, and he was halfway out.
警方认为  他可能中途后悔了
They think that... he might have had second thoughts.
如果我去问巴尼·豪尔  他会证实你的话吗
If I speak to Barney Hull, he'll confirm that?
你什么意思  佐伊
What are you suggesting, Zoe?
也许有人谋杀了他
Maybe there was foul play.
要是有任何谋杀的迹象
If there was a hint of foul play,
你觉得警方会不去调查吗
don't you think the police would have investigated?
就这些掩盖他酒驾的警察吗
The same police that buried his DUI?
你认为我也脱不了干系
And you think I was involved.
你们之间有联系
There's a connection between you.
听听你在说什么  荒唐至极
listen to you. You sound ludicrous.
我只是问问而已
I'm just asking questions.
不  你这是在瞎猜  瞎联系
No, you're connecting dots that don't exist.
你想让我别插手  装作什么都不知道
You want me to just walk away? Act as if I don't know anything?
没错  是我替彼得解了围
Yes, I got Peter out of a jam.
没错  我让他去找科佩尼科
Yes, I sent him to speak to Kapeniak.
但除此之外  就没别的了
But beyond that, there's nothing to know.
别怪我  但现在我实在没法相信你的话
Can you blame me if I find it difficult to trust you right now?
信不信随你
Trust me or not,
我很快就要被正式任命为副总统了
but I'm about to be confirmed as the vice president.
我们的合作关系已经延伸到总统层面了
And our relationship extends to the Oval Office now.
别无缘无故地没事找事
Don't step out of the sunlight for no reason.
让我们忘记过去  展开新的合作
Let's start this new chapter with a clean slate.
你回去好好想想  我会联系你
Now you sleep on that, and I'll be in touch.
我们先做血液和激素检测
We'll start with blood and hormone tests.
结果几天之内就能出来
Those results should be back within a few days.
如果结果不错
If they're good,
我们就开始对你和你丈夫进行基因检测
we'll move on to genetic testing for both you and your husband.
你和他谈过了吗
Have you spoken to him yet?
还没有  我想先做检测
Not yet. I want to do the tests first.
这周什么时间做都可以
We can do those anytime this week.
我会让我的人跟你这边联络
I'll have my office call yours.
差点忘了
I almost forgot.
我上网做了些研究
I've been doing some research on the Internet.
网上的话不能都信啊
Be careful of the Internet.
我在搜索四十岁以上孕妇的
Well, I was looking into common issues
孕期常见问题时
associated with post-40 pregnancies,
查到了一个药物
and this drug came up.
但是没查到什么详细信息  它叫静脉
But there wasn't much on it. It's Cruvenae...
静脉雌酮
Cruvenae-tenuestrin.
你没找到详细信息是因为这种药
You probably haven't found much because it's,
还处在测试阶段
still in the beta stage.
这药物有什么疗效
And what does it do?
它能促进胎盘的血液流动
It helps maximize blood flow to the placenta.
此前还没有哪种药物能做到这一点
Until CVT there hasn't been any viable drug for that.
这药目前仍有争议
The jury's still out.
但是各年龄段的女性都可能患上胎盘机能不全
But placental insufficiency affects women of all ages.
你现在先别担心这个
I wouldn't worry about it for now.
我们还是按部就班  慢慢来
That's putting the cart way before the horse.
马修斯已经稳操胜券
You know, Matthews has this locked up,
但是国会保守人士认为
but conservatives on the hill are saying
他这次重回州长之位  还会像从前一样
he's gonna return to Harrisburg with the same myopic,
目光短浅  增加赤字
deficit-growing mentality.
至于马修斯获胜后接任副总统的人选
Now, as to who's gonna replace Matthews when he wins...
我把墙灯关上不碍事吧
Can I at least turn off the overhead?
当然没事
Of course.
...还能有谁在财政上更恣意妄为...
...someone even more fiscally irresponsible...
需要我去楼下工作吗
Do you want me to go work downstairs?
不用  没事  给我腾个地方就行
No. That's fine. Just make some room.
你还没表态呢
You haven't said a word.
是的
No.
那我们怎么办
Where does that leave us?
我完全准备好了
I'm fully prepared.
早就蓄势待发了
And I have been for some time.
我知道你会做出你认为最好的决定
I know you'll do whatever you think is best.
但是安德伍德确认了
But Underwood confirmed it.
他将被推举为副总统
He's gonna be tapped for VP.
那对我们一点帮助也没有
That doesn't get us any closer.
我们知道罗素的死给马修斯扫清了障碍
Well, we know that Russo cleared the way for Matthews.
只能印证理论  但不是证据
It reinforces the theory. It doesn't give us proof.
我们不能指责他耍卑鄙手段
We can't go after the guy for playing dirty.
那根本不算新闻
That's not news.
国会里一半的混蛋都在耍手段
Half the fuckers in Congress play dirty.
他扶持一个假候选人  就为到时搞垮他
He propped up a sham candidate, just to take him down.
那天晚上没人强迫罗素喝酒
Nobody forced Russo to drink that night.
那家伙本来就是个酒鬼
The guy was an alcoholic.
好吧  除了三天后他自杀了
Okay, we don't know what happened that night,
关于那晚我们一无所知
other than three days later he killed himself.
你还会再联系他吗
Are you gonna contact him again?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们得放慢进度
We need to slow down,
退一步重新考虑
take a step back, and reevaluate.
我们已经让瑞秋溜走了
We already let Rachel slip away.
除非掌握更多信息  否则都是徒劳
There's no point until we have more.
我们应该让他去猜  而不是
We should keep him guessing, not --
等等  从哪里掌握更多信息  从谁那里
Wait-- have more from where? From who?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我们应该先尝试别的办法
But we should exhaust all options
让佐伊再去联系安德伍德只是下策
before Zoe reaches back out to Underwood.
那会显得我们太心急
It looks desperate.
但我们别无选择
But we don't have any options.
我们已经撞南墙了
We are up against a brick wall.
除非安德伍德
And unless Underwood--
佐伊
Zoe...?
我需要一个人想想
I just need to think.
大家一起讨论吧
Well, let's think about it together.
明天给你打电话
I'll call you tomorrow.
弗莱迪
Freddy?
怎么了  弗兰克
Yeah, Frank?
今早的肋排是不是有什么不同
Was there something different about these ribs this morning?
更好吃了还是难吃了
Better or worse?
我本以为你的肋排是美味到极致了
I didn't think that they could get any better,
不过今天的真是不同凡响
but these were something special.
换了一个新屠夫
Well, tried a new butcher.
他慢慢地给猪放血
Slow-bleeds his hogs.
这屠宰方法不合法  但是...
It ain't legal, but...
我不会告诉别人的
Well, I won't tell anyone.
我不知道还会不会再去他那里买肉
I don't know if I'm gonna go back to him.
我去他的店
Went out to his shop.
店后有个房间
He's got a room in the back
他就在那里杀猪
where he does it.
房间是隔音的  里面装备齐全
Soundproof. A whole setup.
为什么要弄成隔音的
W-- why soundproof?
因为猪叫得太厉害
'Cause of how they scream.
它们能嗅到死神来临的气息
They can smell it coming.
往它们的喉咙里插根管子
You stick that pipe in their throat,
接下来的十分钟简直生不如死
the next 10 minutes is hell.
你的鼓膜都能被震破
Bust your fucking eardrums.
人性化的方式是速战速决
Now, the humane way to do it is to make it quick.
装作喂食那样提一桶泔水来  然后  砰
Bring out a bucket of slop like it's feeding time and -- -- bam.
对准后脑勺来上一锹
Shovel right to the base of the head.
猪一声也不会吭
No screaming.
博奇同意公开竞争  但他说的很清楚
He's willing to open up the race, but Birch was very clear:
如果他不能支持谁  你也不行
if he can't endorse anyone, you can't either.
很公平
That's fair.
你真的希望巴克沃特胜选
You really want Buchwalter to win?
我希望最优秀的人能胜选
I want the best man to win.
谨小慎微的废话  说了等于没说
That sounds like a cagey bullshit non-answer to me.
我不想插手这件事情  泰瑞
I'm on the sidelines for this one, Terry.
什么事你不插手  弗兰克
You're never on the sidelines, Frank.
回头见
I'll see you around.
未知号码  我们能重新开始了吗
克莱尔  你不回我电话
Claire. You wouldn't return my calls.
我就回来
I'll be back.
我的律师说我不应该再和你接触
My attorney said that I shouldn't be in contact with you.
蓝十字会告诉我保险被取消了
Blue Cross said my insurance was canceled.
为会员及其家属提供住院等医疗保险的非赢利组织
解雇金条款里规定了一年的健康保险
The severance package gave me health coverage for up to a year.
好像是的
That sounds right.
所以肯定出了什么问题
So there must be some kind of mistake.
你得去跟保险公司说啊
Well, you'll have to talk to the insurance company.
我去了  他们说保险被终止了
I did. They said it was terminated.
如果雇主不同意  他们就无法恢复
They can't reinstate it without the employer's approval.
你想让我帮你一把
And you want me to get involved?
有一些我需要的药物
There's medication that I need
必须通过健康维护组织获取
that I can't get unless it goes through my HMO.
这我知道  我看过你的档案
I'm well aware. I-- I reviewed your records.
-什么  -你签了同意书
- What? - You signed a consent form.
不  我...我没有
No. I-- I-- I didn't.
你伪造了我的签名吗
You forged my signature?
阿普博姆太太是不是去找过你
Did a Mrs. Applebaum pay you a visit?
你知道你这么做是...
You realize what you're doing is--
民事罪  不是刑事
Civil. Not criminal.
你想清楚了吗  因为等我们上了法庭
Have you thought this out? Because when we go to court--
六个月后吗
You mean six months from now?
你还有四个月就生了  不是吗
You're expecting in four, no?
那么你这四个月就没有药物可用
That's four months without the medicine you need.
如果有必要的话  我宁愿让你的孩子
I'm wiling to let your child wither and die inside you
夭折在你肚子里
if that's what's required.
但我们都不想看到那种结果
But neither of us wants that.
说说看  你真的想和我做敌人吗
Now tell me, am I really the sort of enemy you want to make?
但你还有选择
But here's the alternative.
这家机构  这些员工
This office, this staff,
一年2200万美元都给你
22 million a year could be yours.
净水计划也是你的
The CWI could be yours.
你我的恩怨一笔勾销
And you and me, we wash our hands of each other.
你想收买我
You're trying to buy me.
不  我们初见时我答应给你权力
No. When we first met, I promised to empower you.
我这是在兑现诺言
I'm fulfilling that promise.
你骗我怎么办
How do I get screwed?
不会的  我辞职  你取代我的职位
You don't. I resign. You take my place.
没其他条件吗
No strings?
没有
None.
民调显示吉姆·马修斯
Exit polls have Jim Matthews winning
将以9到12个百分点的绝对优势赢得竞选
by anywhere from a nine-to-twelve-percent margin of victory.
喂
Hello?
安德伍德太太吗
Mrs. Underwood?
我是
Yes.
你好  这里是拉森医生办公室
Hi. I'm calling from Dr. Larson's office
跟您确认一下明早十点的血检和尿检
to confirm your 10 a.m. tomorrow for the blood and urine tests.
我去不了
I can't come.
如果明天不行
Well, if tomorrow doesn't work,
我们可以重新安排到周四  甚至周一
we can reschedule for Thursday or even Monday--
不  别给我安排了
No, I won't be rescheduling.
请替我感谢拉森医生的会诊
Please tell Dr. Larson I appreciate all her consultation,
但我经过再三考虑
but I've put a great deal of thought into this
我不会再进行其他检测了
and I won't be pursuing any further tests.
谢谢
Thank you.
你考虑过我们之前讨论的事了吗
Have you thought about what we discussed?
你说得没错  我们是该抛开过去  重新开始
I think you're right. We should start with a clean slate.
我们的短信呢
What about our text messages?
全部删除
还有通讯录
And the contact?
删除
我们之间没事吧
Are we good?
没事
Yeah.
我们忘记这些乱七八糟的事
And we can put all this other nonsense behind us
互相信任  互相帮助  可以吗
and trust one another and continue to help one another?
这样很好
I'd like that.
那现在算是抛开过去了
Then consider the slate clean.
回答我个问题
Answer me one thing.
副驾座的事
The passenger seat.
你说罗素是想出去
You said Russo was trying to get out.
这没什么奇...
That there was nothing ab--
我们不是刚刚说好...
I thought we just agreed to--
我想相信你  但你得说明白
I want to believe you, but I need details.
你没说出来的信息
More than what you're sharing.
你想问什么
What's your question?
罗素酒瘾复发当晚  他出席了一个募捐活动
The night Russo fell off the wagon he was at a fundraiser.
麦克奈利癌症研究所...
The McNeally Cancer Institute--
警察报告里全都有
All in the police report.
瑞秋·波斯纳当晚也在那家酒店
Rachel Posner was at the hotel that night.
那是谁
Who's that?
罗素被捕时跟他在一起的应召女
The call girl who was with Russo when he was arrested.
我又不知道她叫什么
I didn't know her name.
她消失了  弗兰西斯
She disappeared, Francis.
什么时候
When?
别装不知道  我给行李员看了张照片
Don't act surprised. I showed the bellmen a photo.
其中一个记得见过她
One of them remembers seeing her.
她是个妓女
The girl's a prostitute.
她肯定经常出现在各种酒店
I'm sure she frequents many hotels.
可偏巧那晚去那家酒店吗
But that hotel on that night?
你这语气像斯克斯基小姐似的
Well, now you sound like Ms. Skorsky talking.
我没和任何人说过这事
I haven't discussed this with anyone.
我想先问你
I wanted to ask you first.
我不知道那晚发生了什么
I have no idea what happened that night,
只知道彼得又开始酗酒
except that Peter started drinking again.
我不知道有谁在场
I don't know who was or wasn't there.
真希望我在
I wish I was.
说不定我能阻止他
Maybe I could have stopped him.
你知道瑞秋在哪吗
Do you know where Rachel is?
相信我的话
Listen to what I am saying.
我是想要保护我们两个人
I am trying to protect us both.
谁都有可能问这些问题
These are questions anyone could ask.
但现在只有你在问
But no one is, except you.
我真不知你想干什么
I can't imagine what you're after.
我冒了个险
I took a chance.
跑去你家  任你摆布
Showed up at your house and placed myself at your feet.
于公于私都跨过了道德底线
Crossed ethical lines, professionally, physically.
我愿意为这些事情负责
And I hold myself accountable for that.
这都是我的选择  我愿意承担后果
Those were my choices, and I can live with them.
我也希望向前看
I'd like to move forward,
但我需要知道我到底卷入了什么事
but I need to know exactly what I was a part of.
我要确定我没有卷入...
That... that I wasn't a part of someone's...
把话说完
Finish your thought.
一起谋杀
Part of someone's murder.
天哪
Jesus.
我想要相信你  弗兰西斯
I want to believe you, Francis.
我知道你
I know you --
简宁
Janine!
快进来
Come in.
我打不通你电话
I've been calling you.
进屋坐吧
Come in. Sit down.
喝点什么吗
Um, you -- you want something?
水  或者果汁
Some, uh, water or, um, juice?
你要出门
You going somewhere?
你要去哪
Hey. You going somewhere?
去我妈妈那里  在伊萨卡
To my mom's. In Ithaca.
-什么  -我要走了
- What? - I'm leaving.
不不  不行
No. No, no, no. No. No way.
-我们什么都没有  -你要放弃吗
- We have nothing. - Are you giving up on this?
这世上只有三个人知道他干了什么
There are only three people in the world that know what he has done,
其中一个已经死了
and one of them is gone.
如果我们有证据  卢卡斯
If we had anything, Lucas,
任何确凿证据
any hard evidence
哪怕是一个愿意公开的信息源
or even a fucking quote from a source that would go on record for us,
那也好说
that would be one thing.
可我们纯粹在捕风捉影  而他不是闹着玩的
But we are grasping, and he is not fucking around.
是你说服佐伊追查这事的
You were the one who told Zoe to pursue this.
她告诉了我你说的话
She told me what you said.
能把你吓坏的文章才是真正重要的
The only stories that mattered were the ones that scared you to death.
这可不仅仅是死亡威胁
Okay, this isn't just death threats.
这是来真的
This is real.
他不知道你  但他知道我
He doesn't know about you, but he knows about me.
这是在我邮箱里发现的
These were in my mailbox.
没有发信地址
No return address.
他照了她的照片
He took these of her?
还能是谁  你留着吧
Who else? You can keep them.
但我不认为这对你有什么帮助
But I don't think they're gonna help you.
我们必须阻止他
We need to stop him.
变态混蛋
Sick fucking shit.
简宁  你不能就这么逃跑
Janine, you cannot run away from this!
我这一辈子从来都找硬骨头啃
My entire career, I have always chosen the tough stories.
我一向无所畏惧
I have been fearless.
可你猜怎么着
But you know what?
我这回真的害怕极了
I'm really fucking scared this time.
他重权在握
He's got power.
他输不起
He's got a lot to lose.
现在他完全占了上风
And right now he is winning.
拜托  我需要你帮助  别这样
Please, I need your help. Please, don't do this.
别做梦了  卢卡斯
Just wake the fuck up, Lucas!
事故发生于昨晚八点左右
The incident occurred at approximately eight p.m. last night
在大教堂高地地铁站北向的列车轨道上
on the northbound tracks of the Cathedral Heights metro station.
华盛顿特区警察已经判定是一起意外
D.C. Police have ruled the death an accident.
佐伊·巴恩斯是头条网的资深撰稿人
Zoe Barnes was a senior contributor at slugline.com.
佐伊·巴恩斯  地铁悲剧  新闻界对事故表示哀悼
此前她曾在《华盛顿先驱报》
Previously she worked at the Washington Herald
做都市新闻记者和政治记者
as a metro reporter and political correspondent.
巴恩斯报道过多条重要新闻
Barnes broke several major stories,
包括教育改革法案的草案
include an early draft of the Education Reform and Achievement Act,
以及导致迈克尔·科恩参议员
as well as a college newspaper article
未能被提名国务卿的
that derailed Senator Michael Kern's
一篇公报社论
nomination for Secretary of State...
你觉得那些文件怎么样
What'd you think of the files?
有不少可以下手的地方
There's plenty to work with.
你看了自己的吗
Did you look at your own?
里面什么都没有
There was nothing there.
里面该有什么吗
Should there be?
不应该
No.
即便你在撒谎
Even if you're lying,
但我现在什么也没找到
the fact that I haven't been able to find anything
这说明你很擅长隐藏踪迹
tells me you're very good at covering your tracks.
这点对我来说很宝贵  这里就是我们的战场
That's, uh, valuable to me. Here's our battleground.
113票
113 votes.
看来你已经掌握大致情况了
You have the skeletons.
如果我失败了  他们不会放过我
If I lose, they'll come after me.
这是你必须承担的风险
That's a risk you have to take.
我怎么知道你不是在利用我
How do I know you're not just using me?
为别人竞选制造障碍
Throwing a wrench into someone else's bid?
那是另一种风险  你也可以选择等上十年
That's another risk. The alternative is you wait 10 years.
你选我肯定是有原因的
You chose me for a reason.
我想知道是什么
I'd like to know what it is.
好吧
All right.
你发起过多少次导弹攻击
How many missile strikes did you launch?
多到让我整夜不能安睡
Enough to keep me awake at night.
但你还是那么做了
But you did it anyway.
是的  没错
Yes, I did.
会伤及多少妇女儿童
How many women and children?
太多了
Too many.
就算知道会伤及无辜
And you launched those missiles
你还是义无反顾地发射了导弹
knowing all those innocent people would die.
我是奉命歼灭敌人
I had orders to eliminate the enemy.
而你专业高效地完成了任务
Which you carried out expertly and efficiently.
你杀过人吗
Have you ever killed anyone?
没有
No.
我曾亲眼目睹整栋大楼  整个村庄荡然无存
I watched apartment buildings, entire villages gone,
就像不曾存在过
like they were never there.
如果可以  我不想再谈这个话题了
I'd prefer not to talk about it, if that's all right.
你完成需要完成的任务
You did what needed to be done,
这就是我选择你的原因  杰姬
and that's why I chose you, Jackie.
服役背景  历史清白
Service background. Clean history.
上相  我全都看好
Photogenic. The whole package.
但更重要的是
But more importantly,
坚决  务实
ruthless pragmatism.
我们能合作吗
Are we working together or not?
有公开或私下表示支持巴克沃特吗
Any public or private endorsements for Buchwalter,
我支持韦伯
I come out for Webb.
我不参与争论  我向你保证
I'll stay out of the fray. I give you my word.
你也一样  泰瑞
Same goes for you, Terry.
谢谢  克里斯蒂娜
Thank you, Christina.
先生们
Gentlemen.
总统先生  宾州情况怎么样
Mr. President. How was Pennsylvania?
喜欢印度菜吗
You like Indian?
先生  我看到新闻了
Sir? I've seen the news.
我知道她跟您很亲近
I know she was close to you.
可怕的悲剧啊
Terrible tragedy.
今天特别探员洛克兰来找过我  先生
Spoke to Special Agent Rockland today, sir.
我下周开始培训
I begin my training next week.
很好
Very good.
我知道已经晚了一天
I know it's a day late.
但愿这样不失妥当
Hope it isn't inappropriate,
我想给您这个
but I wanted to give you this.
谢谢  密查姆
Thank you, Meechum.
艾德华真是太贴心了
That was very nice of Edward.
他不该为我花这种钱
He shouldn't have spent this sorta money on me.
我在楼下开了酒
I've opened some wine downstairs.
我就下去
I'll be down in a minute.
你以为我把你忘了吗
Did you think I'd forgotten you?
也许你希望我已经忘了
Perhaps you hoped I had.
别浪费时间哀悼巴恩斯小姐了
Don't waste a breath mourning Ms. Barnes.
每只小猫都会长大
Every kitten grows up to be a cat.
一开始看起来都很无害
They seem so harmless at first.
幼小  安静  舔着浅盘里的牛奶
Small, quiet, lapping up their saucer of milk.
但爪子一旦长长了  猫就会挠人
But once their claws get long enough, they draw blood.
有时甚至会挠养猫人的手
Sometimes from the hand that feeds them.
对于我们这些爬向食物链顶端的人来说
For those of us climbing to the top of the food chain,
决不能心慈手软
there can be no mercy.
只有一条规则  不做猎人  便为猎物
There is but one rule: hunt or be hunted.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
弗兰克见杰姬时  墙上的著名照片中的两人分别是
美国第36任总统林登·约翰逊[左]和理查德·拉塞尔[右]
拉塞尔是佐治亚州参议员
曾一度被认为是林登·约翰逊政治上的导师和引路人之一
但约翰逊担任总统后  拉塞尔在《民权法案》问题上与约翰逊对立
而约翰逊为推动法案通过  对拉塞尔毫不留情
约翰逊被认为是美国近代历史上最会耍弄权术的总统和政客
为达目的无所不用其极
但同时也被认为是美国历史上最伟大的总统之一
在任上通过了《民权法案》  建立晚年医保制度
完善美国社会保障体系  为美国社会进步做出巨大贡献
在第一季中
弗兰克办公室桌上便放了一本新出版的约翰逊传记
《通往权力之路》
美国第35任总统肯尼迪在达拉斯被枪手刺杀
2小时8分钟后  副总统约翰逊接任肯尼迪的职务
成为美国第36任总统
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
翻译 草草   somehacker   卫老哥   章鱼X
翻译 喃喃   肉松   香茗小焙   小饭
时间轴 吉吉   aaaBao   旅行的木讷   后期 饿得慌
校对 草草   总监 草草
《纸牌屋》
第一季  第一集